Alright
In today's lesson
we're going to talk about custom wake-up words
Before we dive into this topic
let's fix a bug
Let's take a look at the code here
Right here
Okay
We don't need to handle this channel here
Because when we make the call
Let's take a look
When making this call
We have already specified how many channels to retrieve here
It has already been passed in here
So when we retrieve it here
The channel number has already been calculated
This is a dual-channel setup
It has already been calculated here
So, we'll comment that out.
Then, let's take a look at the effect, shall we?
Hi, Xiao Zhou.
Ah, it recognized it, right?
We can try calling out some other names as well.
Hi, Xiao Zhi.
See, it recognized that too.
Xiao Zhi was recognized as well.
The score is 0.8, huh.
Um
So then
it's not the welcome message we specified
which means he didn't print that sentence
this sentence indicates we've found the phantom word
and we've already done this
we added it here
you can add any phantom word
this is the custom method
You can add whatever you like using the Pinyin method.
Using this Pinyin method.
We've added quite a few here.
And now we're using HII Xiao Zhou.
Let's give it another try.
Hi, Xiao Zhou.
See, it recognized it, right?
That's how it gets activated.
This is similar to the wake-up word.
Then, this is done using command words, you see.
Well, it’s definitely not as good as those phantom words.
Using
those phantom words,
it’s like the Lexing official team has trained us,
with a lot of data,
usually around 20,000 sets,
I think the minimum is 20,000 sets of data.
They conduct vertical training.
It's like using command words.
It's more like a horizontal approach.
A broad direction, you might say.
A more general kind of thing.
It hasn't been specifically trained on this particular phrase.
It has been trained on many characters, though.
And a lot of words as well.
So, it's definitely not as effective.
But, with some optimization, it can still work fine.
If you really think it's not feasible
you should go to the official Lexing website for customization
the details of how to achieve this
I'll put the notes from this video into my notebook.
I'll put it at the bottom of the notes
I'll add the links
we've already implemented this feature
we'll cover the details later
Place it after this video note.
that's all for this lesson